William Giammona

FULL STACK WEB3 DEVELOPER

Profile

Co-founder of GlobalWebThree DAO, a boutique Wyoming-based Decentralized Autonomous Organization focusing on blockchain technology, smart contract creation and front-end development. As a full stack Web3 developer, my expertise spans TypeScript, React, Next.js, Solidity, Python, Moralis, Ethers.js, Hardhat, Truffle, and Foundry.

Employment History

Co-Founder GlobalWebThree DAO

2022 - PRESENT

Co-founder of GlobalWebThree DAO, a boutique Decentralized Autonomous Organization focusing on on blockchain technology, smart contract creation and front-end development. My work encompasses a diverse array of smart contract creation, including Escrow, Raffle, MultiSig, and NFT based smart contracts, as well as integrating them with front-ends.

Mathematics Tutor, Wyzant

2020 - 2022

At Wyzant, an online tutoring platform, I served as a Mathematics tutor specializing in Trigonometry/Pre-Calculus, Algebra 2, and Geometry. Leveraging my comprehensive understanding of these subjects, I simplified complex concepts and developed individualized learning strategies for students.

Israel teaching fellow, MASA, Netanya, Israel

2018 - 2019

At the Masa Israel Teaching Fellowship in Netanya, Israel, I had the opportunity to teach English as a second language to refugees and underprivileged children. I utilized tailored teaching methodologies to help these students gain language proficiency, instilling in them a sense of confidence and love of learning.

Financial Tax Associate, Ernst & Young, San Francisco

2017

At EY, I primarily worked on preparing K-1 tax information for financial LLP's including hedge-funds, private-equity funds, and venture-capital funds. In addition to working with partnerships, I also worked on federal and state corporate tax returns for the Charles Schwab Corporation.

Education

B.A. Economics and Accounting, University of California, Santa Barbara

2012 - 2016

Electrical Engineering Program, Tel Aviv University, Tel Aviv

2019 - 2021

Courses

Free Code Camp Full Stack Web3 Development Course, 2022

Details

+972535698285 wgiammona@gmail.com

PLACE OF BIRTH

United States

Links

GlobalWebThree Website
Github

Skills

Foundry

Hardhat

Truffle

Solidity

Typescript

Python

HTML & CSS

React.js

Next.js

Ethers.js

Moralis

Languages

English (Native)

Hebrew

Spanish